Deity.  At the end of
summer, I pick
hibiscus flowers.  I
like to dry
them on the windowsill and
then mix them with
boiling water, lemon, and a
pinch of something
sweet.  This taste
for me signifies
the end of the long
hot season and the
imminent arrival of the
fall harvest.
Today I decided to
take you with me to
my bookstore and
show you a little bit about my
work life.
Forest fires
recently closed a
mountain pass that
many tourists use to come to our country.  That's why it's
unusually
quiet and sleepy here now.
I usually have breakfast in the
city, it's not a very
good habit, but
sometimes it works out that way.
I now make
$17 an hour because I
now manage
our bookstore's
Instagram page, which is an added
responsibility.  What do
you think?  Good.  So,
I just opened
the store, and now I'm
going to go around it to
see what
needs to be cleaned before the
official opening
.  Then I need to
look into the warehouse,
check the remaining
goods and do other
work.  Maybe I'll
dust it off a little.  And
if I have free
time, I'll rearrange something
or arrange it
alphabetically—this is a
constant and very
important part of
working in a bookstore.
Books
get out of
place pretty quickly.  Since
the store is
pretty tidy right now, I think that's what
I'll
do now.  So I'm going to
put everything in
alphabetical order.  And if,
like me, you have to
hum
the alphabet quietly all the time, it will be a
long process.
I'll start with
fiction, and
we'll see from there.  And soon
, in about an hour, we
will be ready to
open.  It's a pretty
routine job with
a lot of cleaning, and
I like it.
Some may find it
boring, but for me
it's calming.  From time to
time I talk about
books with buyers, and
it's always nice.
Iger wants you to
pay attention to
his bandana because
he
looks really good today.
Of course?  Don't you
look good today?  Yes.  So,
one of the benefits of working
at a bookstore is,
of course, the discount on
books, but more
importantly, you
get early
versions of e-books
and audiobooks, as well as
print editions.
So, here's how it works:
publishers send out
paper books, and
also provide access
to audiobooks and
e-books
months, sometimes even a
year, before the
book's official release date.  This is
done so that
booksellers and
other
book lovers can
get early
access and provide
feedback and first
impressions to the author and
his team.
For example, here's a stack of
preview
copies we
received in the mail
recently.  Alice
Hoffman's book The Invisible
Hour has already been released,
but we received a
preview
copy a few
months ago, so we
were able to read it
in advance and
write a review.  As
an artist and a dreamer, I
like to romanticize
my work,
no matter
what I'm doing—at home or in a
bookstore.  But it's important
to note that this is a
job like any
other.  There are days
when I get tired and
make mistakes.
Not every day is
perfect, but every
day is meaningful, and there
is always something to
be grateful for.
So I learned
to accept these ups and
downs.  After
closing the store, I'm
usually pretty
tired and
looking forward to
the opportunity to give my
feet a rest.  So
I go home to have dinner
with my husband, spend
time with my
pets,
and hopefully
do some reading before bed.
I hope you
enjoyed this
little day.  He's
not very exciting.
My work life isn't that
interesting, but
it means a lot to me
.  So I
decided to share
it, and I hope it
brings you some
peace this evening.
Overall, it was a
great day.  And I
got home just in time,
fortunately, because it's the
height of summer.  It's
still very light outside.  So I
thought I'd show
you some of the books I
brought
home today.  I'll start with ARCs,
that is,
introductory
copies for
readers.  All these books are
free here.  They
were sent to us as
booksellers in the
hope that we would
review them.  However,
they are already very old.
All of these books have been published
and are on
sale for a long time.  So these are
just old
copies
lying around doing nothing.
So I decided to
show them to you.
The first of them is "The Road of
the Lost."  It's about
Kroy, who is a brownie, a
fairy-tale
creature.  This seems like a
very adventurous,
perhaps a bit
dangerous story
, with lots of curses,
invisibility, and spells.
So, I think that
sounds pretty
exciting.  This is a very
old book.  It seems like
it was published a
few years ago,
but it's "The Extremely
Inconvenient Adventures of
Bronte Nettlestone."
It's a story about a very
developed girl
who receives instructions
from her parents in a will
to go
on an adventure, and it's just a
silly and
incredibly funny
journey.  The last
free
paperback
I picked up was "The
Awakening Forest."  Its
cover seemed
a bit
scary to me.  I'm not one to
read
creepy horror or
suspense novels.  However, this
book seemed
interesting to me.  So I
decided to give her a chance
.  It tells the story of a
witch who lives in the forest
on a throne of carved
bones and waits for
children who will beg her in their dreams
to grant their
wishes.  This seemed
quite
intriguing to me.  So,
let's try to
get out of our
comfort zone a little.  I don't quite
understand what exactly
has changed in me as a
person and as a
reader.  I used to
really like
darker stories,
horror stories,
true crimes, and
things like that.  I
enjoyed them much more
when I was younger.
Maybe it's because I've had some
really
scary things happen in my life, and it's
ruined everything a bit.  It
just stopped
seeming even a little
fun to me.  It
only reminded me of
my own fears.  This is
not a criticism at all
if you like dark
and creepy stories.
On the contrary, I respect you a lot
because I'm...well, I'm
just a very sensitive
person.  I also
ordered two
paperback books, which I
think sound
pretty exciting.  I
love using
the library when I
can, but these books
weren't in my local library, and
I really wanted to
read them.  So I
also wanted
to support the authors,
because the first book is
"Kenny and the Book of
Beasts" by Tony
Dieterlizzi.  This is the second
part of the
Kenny and the Dragon series, and I
think it's just a
magical story with
beautiful
illustrations.  He's
one of my
favorite
artists of all
time, so I felt
compelled to
support his new
work.  I also picked up
"Echoes of the North" by
Joanna Ruth Meyer.  I do
n't know too much
about the plot, only that it was
recommended to me by a few
people.  It seems to have a
lot of the atmosphere of the
magical snowy
countryside where
I live for four,
five or six
months of the year.  So I
thought this would be a
perfect winter
read.  Quite a
significant change in genres.
I purchased the second
book in the series "The
Big Panda and the
Little Dragon" by
James Norbury.
Norbury, Norbury.
It's about two
adorable characters
named Panda and
Little Dragon.
They have so much
wisdom and a
beautiful vision of
their world.  In this
story, Little
Dragon tries
to find a deeper meaning in
his life.  He
feels
lost, unsure of
how to achieve
self-realization, so
they set off
on a journey together.  If you
like the book "
The Boy, the Mole, the Fox
and the Horses", then this one is very
similar to it.  The last
book I picked up was "The
Green Wilderness" by
Peri Thompson.  It
has a great
cover design and
seems to be
about a community of
magical botanists,
where the plants are very
unique and have
magical properties.
They can grow and
change shape, the
plants in this story are
intelligent, and there are these
beautiful whimsical
illustrations.  So I
really, really want to
finish reading it,
because I've already started it.  I'm already
on page 88.  And
finally, I didn't take the
book.  I purchased a
set of information
cards about plants.
You see an image of
the plant, and on the back
is all the information about
it.  Not just
the story, but also the
symbolism, how
to collect it and how
to use it.
For example, here is
purslane.  These
illustrations were created by
herbalist Elizabeth
Blackwell, who is a
fascinating
person and I
think she is an
incredible
artist.  So, these are the
books I
brought home today.  As a
bookseller, I don't
often bring
books home.  I definitely
developed
self-control, but this
was a special occasion,
so I decided to take
a few titles that I had
been eyeing for a long time.
Thank you all for
supporting this
channel through my
Etsy shop.  And
I hope if you
stop by the
bookstore, you'll
say hello if I'm
there.  Sending
you lots of love.
I hope you
enjoyed this video.
Goodbye.